<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Containers>
  <Name>Zoneminder</Name>
  <Date>2015-10-27</Date>
  <Description>
    Zoneminder is the top Linux video camera security and surveillance solution. [br][br]
    [b][u][span style='color: #E80000;']Configuration[/span][/u][/b][br]
    [b]/config[/b] This is where the zoneminder configuration and library files will reside[br][br]
    Don't forget to enter in the host port and app folder.
  </Description>
  <Overview>
    [b][u][span style='color: #E80000;']This container has been deprecated. Please install version 1.29 instead[/span][/u][/b][br]Zoneminder is the top Linux video camera security and surveillance solution. ZoneMinder is intended for use in single or multi-camera video security applications, including commercial or home CCTV, theft prevention and child, family member or home monitoring and other domestic care scenarios such as nanny cam installations. It supports capture, analysis, recording, and monitoring of video data coming from one or more video or network cameras attached to a Linux system. ZoneMinder also support web and semi-automatic control of Pan/Tilt/Zoom cameras using a variety of protocols. It is suitable for use as a DIY home video security system and for commercial or professional video security and surveillance. It can also be integrated into a home automation system via X.10 or other protocols. If you're looking for a low cost CCTV system or a more flexible alternative to cheap DVR systems then why not give ZoneMinder a try?
  </Overview>
  <Support>http://lime-technology.com/forum/index.php?topic=39413.0</Support>
  <Registry>https://registry.hub.docker.com/u/aptalca/docker-zoneminder/</Registry>
  <GitHub>https://github.com/aptalca/docker-zoneminder</GitHub>
  <Repository>aptalca/docker-zoneminder</Repository>
  <BindTime>true</BindTime>
  <Privileged>true</Privileged>
    <Networking>
    <Mode>bridge</Mode>
    <Publish>
      <Port>
        <HostPort></HostPort>
        <ContainerPort>80</ContainerPort>
        <Protocol>tcp</Protocol>
      </Port>
    </Publish>
  </Networking>
  <Environment>
    <Variable>
      <Name></Name>
      <Value></Value>
    </Variable>
  </Environment>    
  <Data>
    <Volume>
      <HostDir></HostDir>
      <ContainerDir>/config</ContainerDir>
      <Mode>rw</Mode>
    </Volume>
  </Data>
  <WebUI>http://[IP]:[PORT:80]/zm</WebUI>
  <Banner></Banner>
  <Icon>http://www.pddesign.com.au/img/blog/home-surveillance/zoneminder-logo-01.png</Icon>
  <Beta>False</Beta>
  <Category>HomeAutomation: MediaApp:Video MediaServer:Video Tools:</Category>
  <Changes>
    [center][font size=5]Zoneminder Change Log[/font][/center]
    
    [font size=4]2015.10.27[/font]
    - perl5/ZoneMinder folder is now persistent and available in the config folder to allow easy access for custom perl scripts
    - usbutils included for usb camera support (needs to be tested)
    
    [font size=4]2015.06.13[/font]
    - Incorporated memory fix for HD and multiple cameras
    - Switched back to the phusion base
    - [b]You may have to delete your local data folder and start from scratch[/b]

  </Changes>
</Containers>
